片名：宇宙威龙
道格?
Doug?
亲爱的，你还好吧
Honey, are you all right?
你又作梦了
You're dreaming.
道格，是否又是关于火星的梦?
Doug, was it about Mars?
好点没?
Is that better?
我可怜的宝贝
My poor baby.
这些梦都快占据你的脑袋了
This is getting to be an obsession.
她也在梦里吗？
Was she there?
谁?
Who?
那个你对我提过的褐发女子
The one you told me about. the brunette.
罗莉
Lori.
我不敢相信连我作梦你也会吃醋
I can't believe you're jealous of a dream.
- 她到底是谁? - 无足轻重的人
- Who is she? - Nobody.
无足轻重的人？她叫什么名字？
'Nobody'? What's her name?
我不知道
I don't know.
- 告诉我！ - 我不知道啊！
- Tell me! - I don't know!
你最好是告诉我！
You better tell me!
这可不好笑，道格 你每天晚上都梦到她啊！
It's not funny, Doug. You dream about her every night.
但我到了早上总回到你身边
And I'm always back in the morning.
放开我！
Let me go!
别这样，宝贝
Come on, baby.
你知道，你才是我梦想中的女孩
You know you're the girl of my dreams.
你这是真心话？
You mean it?
你很清楚我是真心的
You know I do.
让我给你的春梦提供些题材
I'll give you something to dream about.
主席为这次攻击辩护 宣称在太空中布署的武器
The chairman defended the attack, saying that space-based weapons...
是唯一能对付南区新兴势力的有效防御
are our only effective defense against the southern block's numerical superiority.
此外，火星咋晚又发生暴乱
And more violence last night on Mars...
要求独立的恐怖份子
where terrorists demanding independence...
再度迫使Ｔ矿的开采停工
once again halted the extraction of terbinium ore.
寡头和他率领的所谓自由战土
Kuato and his so-called freedom brigade...
宣称这次爆炸事件是他们所干的
claimed credit for this latest bombing,
企图重新开启 已封闭的金字塔形矿坑
which attempted to reopen the sealed-off Pyramid Mines.
火星军事当局仅以最少的兵力，就恢复当地秩序
Mars military restored order with minimal use of force...
所有重要的战略设施，都在一小时内修复完毕
and all damage to the strategic facility was repaired within hours.
不准拍摄！滚！
No cameras!
目前已经有一处矿坑关闭 火星行政官维罗斯?科海根
With one mine already closed, mars administrator Vilos Cohaagen...
誓言在必要时仍将动用军队
vowed that troops would be used if necessary...
以维持足额的开采量 在今天的记者会中
to keep production at full capacity. At the press conference today
难怪你会做恶梦 你老喜欢看新闻
No wonder you're having nightmares. you're always watching the news.
- 罗莉 - 道格？
- Lori. - Doug?
- 咱们就这么办吧！ - 做什么？
- Let's do it. - Do what?
搬到火星去住
Move to Mars.
亲爱的，你为什么一定要 破坏一个如此美好的早晨呢？
Honey, why do you have to spoil a perfectly wonderful morning?
考虑一下吧
Just think about it.
亲爱的，我们已经谈过无数次了 你会讨厌住在火星上的
Sweetheart, we've been through this a million times. You'd hate it on Mars.
那里既干燥，丑陋，又无趣
It's dry, it's ugly, it's boring.
更何况… 那里随时都可能爆发革命
I mean, really, a revolution could break out there any second.
科海根说那只是一小撮偏激份子
Cohaagen says it's just a few extremists.
你相信他的说法？
You believe him?
好吧，就当我没提过此事
Okay. Forget about it.
绝对不行！ 火星是北区投下大量经费，才殖民成功的
Absolutely not. Mars was colonized by the northern block at enormous expense.
我们全部的军费都得依赖此地的Ｔ矿开采
Our entire war effort depends on their terbinium.
将这一切放弃是荒唐的想法
And it's ridiculous to think we're going to give it away...
就只因为一些懒惰的变种人…
just because a bunch of lazy mutants think they own the planet.
道格，或许咱们该去做一次旅行
- Doug, Maybe we should take a trip, hum? - Any comments, sir, on the rumor
罗莉，拜托别挡住银幕
- Lori, move. - that you've blown the Pyramid Mine...
because you found alien artifacts inside?
还有许多比火星更好的地方啊！
There's a lot better places here than Mars.
土星怎样？ 你不想到土星去看看吗?
What about Saturn? don't you wanna see Saturn?
I wish we could find some alien artifacts. our tourist industry could use a boost.
大家都说那里好漂亮
Everybody says that its gorgeous.
事实是寡头先生和他的恐怖份子 企图散布这些谣言
But the fact is, it's Mr. Kuato and his terrorists who spread these rumors...
以损害人民对政府的信任
to undermine my trust in the government.
我们可以做一次长途的太空之旅 那种无须刻意做任何事的旅行
We could take a long space cruise, the kind with nothing to do.
你说如何？
- Have you found Kuato yet? - We don't even know what he looks like.
你说什么？
- What do you say? - That's all for the news.
我快迟到了，罗莉
- Stay tuned for Christina in the weather. - I'm late.
But first, this.
亲爱的…
- Tonight on ESPN, the fifth game of World Series... - Sweetheart.
live from Tokyo.
道格，我知道刚搬到一个新的城市 是很难适应的，但请你试试看，好吗?
Doug? I know it's hard being in a new town, but let's give it a chance, okay?
罗莉，你难道不明白吗? 我觉得我这辈子不该只是如此
Lori, don't you understand? I feel like I was made for something more than this.
我想在我的一生中有番作为 我想成为一个有用的人
I want to do something with my life, I want to be somebody.
你已经是个了不起的人了
You are somebody.
你是我爱的男人
You're the man I love.
再见
Bye.
祝你有个偷快的一天
Have a nice day.
你现在正进入一个安全地带
You are now entering a safety zone.
所有经核准的武器 都不得携出这检查点
No unauthorized weapons allowed beyond this point.
你现在正进入一个安全地带
You are now entering a safety zone.
所有未经核准的武器
No unauthorized weapons allowed
都不得携出这检查点
beyond this point.
你是否梦想到雪地去滑雪
Would you like to ski...
但却苦无门路…
but you're snowed under with work?
你是否梦想到海底悠游…
Do you dream of a vacation at the bottom of the ocean...
却出不起旅费？
but you can't float the bill?
你是否渴望到火星上爬山…
Have you always wanted to climb the mountains of Mars...
但你的体力却已经走下坡？
but now you're over the hill?
那就到瑞可公司来吧！
Then come to Rekall Incorporated...
你在此可以买到 你心目中理想的假期
where you can buy the memory of your ideal vacation...
比真正的旅游经验更便宜，更安全，更好
cheaper, safer and better than the real thing.
别让美好的人生从你眼前溜过
So don't let life pass you by.
立刻拨电话到瑞可来
Call Rekall for the memory of a lifetime.
给你的生命留下美好的回忆
For the memory of a lifetime
Rekall, Rekall, Rekall
哈利
Harry.
- 你听过瑞可这个公司吧? - 瑞可?
- You ever heard of Rekall? - Rekall?
就是专门卖假记忆的地方
Where they sell those fake memories.
是啊，瑞可！瑞可…
Oh, Rekall.
- 你想去找他们？ - 我不知道，或许吧
- You're thinking of going there? - I don't know, maybe.
- 别去 - 为什么？
- Well, don't. - Why not?
我有一个朋友，试了他的的特殊产品 结果差点得割掉前脑
A friend of mine tried one of these in a special office, nearly got himself lobotomized.
真的?
No shit?
别拿自己脑袋开玩笑，兄弟 不值得
Don't fuck with your brain, pal. It ain't worth it.
我想是吧！
I guess not.
午安，欢迎光临瑞可公司
Good afternoon. welcome to Rekall.
我是道格拉斯?魁德 和医生约好了
Douglas Quaid. I have an appointment.
- 鲍伯？ - 是的
- Bob? - Yeah?
- 道格?魁德来找你了 - 我马上来 - 好
- Doug Quaid is here to see you. - Yeah, I'll be right out. - Okay.
请稍待一下，魁德先生
That'll be just one minute, Mr. Quaid.
谢谢你
Thank you.
- 道格，我是鲍伯?麦克连，幸会 - 幸会
- Doug! Paul McClane. It's good to see ya. - Nice to meet you.
到里面谈吧！这边请
Come on in, through here.
- 坐，不必拘束 - 谢谢你
- Please have a seat, make yourself comfortable. - Thank you.
告诉我，道格
Now, help me out here, Doug.
- 你想要植入的记忆是关于… - 火星
- You were interested in a memory of a-- - Mars.
是啊，火星…
Yeah. Mars.
有困难吗？
Is that a problem?
我老实告诉你好了，道格
To be perfectly honest with you, Doug...
如果你对外层空间感兴趣的话
if outer spaces is your thing...
我想你会更喜欢我们的土星之旅 这是目前最流行的
I think you would be much happier with one of our Saturn cruises. Everybody raves about them.
不，我对土星没兴趣 我要的是火星
No, I'm not interested in Saturn. I said Mars.
好吧！花钱的人是大爷
Okay. You're the boss.
那么就设定在火星
Mars it is.
我看看…
Now, let me see.
一次标准的火星之旅
The basic Mars package...
收费是899个信用单位
will run you 899 credits.
这包括整整两个礼拜的记忆 不但完整，而且非常详细
Now, that's for two full weeks of memories, complete in every detail.
如果你要更久的时间就得再加钱 因为我们得植入更深
If you want a longer trip that'll cost a little more because it's a deeper implant.
两个礼拜的旅程里包括什么？
What's in the two-week package?
首先，我得告诉你，道格 当你到瑞可来，所得到的绝对是第一流的记忆
First of all, Doug. Let me tell you, when you go Rekall, you get nothing but first-class memories.
在航天飞机上接有私人包厢 住宿希尔顿的豪华套房，加上到所有观光点游览
Private cabin in a shuttle, deluxe suite at the Hilton Plaza, all the major sights:
金字塔山，大运河
Mount Pyramid, the Grand Canals...
当然，还有维纳斯城
and, of course, Venusville.
但这些记忆将有多逼真?
But how real does it seem?
- 和你自己的记忆一样逼真 - 少来，别盖我了
- As real as any memory in your head. - Come on, don't bullshit me.
不，我是说真的，道格 你的大脑将分不出它有何差别
No, I'm telling you, Doug. Your brain will not know the difference.
信用保证，不满意可以退钱
That's guaranteed or your money back.
被你们切除前脑的那家伙呢？ 你们事后有退钱给他吗?
What about the guy you lobotomized? did he get a refund?
这是好久以前的事了
You're talking ancient history.
在今天，以瑞可的方式旅行 比搭火箭安全多了
Nowadays traveling with Rekall is safer than getting on a rocket.
你看看那些统计数字
Check out those statistics.
更何况，一次真正的旅程再麻烦不过了
Besides, a real holiday is a pain in the butt.
你会遗失行李，碰上坏天气...
You got lost luggage, lousy weather...
还会被恶出租车司机敲竹杠
crooked taxi drivers.
但当你以瑞可的方式旅行时
When you travel with Rekall...
一切都是完美的
everything is perfect.
你说怎样？
So, what do you say?
- 好吧 - 聪明的决定
- All right. - Smart move.
好，在你填这份调查表的同时
All right, while you fill out this questionnaire,
我顺便向你介绍一下其他的产品
I'll gonna familiarize you with some of our options.
不要其他的产品
No options.
随便你好了 我能问你一个问题吗？
Whatever you say. Can I ask you just one question, though?
在你以往每次的旅行中
What is it? Is it exactly the same...
都有哪一样共同点？
about every single vacation you have ever taken?
我放弃
I give up.
你，你就是那共同点
You. You're the same.
不论你到哪里去，你总是同一个你
No matter where you go, There you are. It's always the same old you.
我建议你这回
Let me suggest that you take a vacation...
暂且不当你自己
from yourself.
我知道这听来很玄
I know, it sounds wild.
这是我们最新的旅行方式 我们称它叫“自我旅行”
It is the latest thing in travel. we call it the Ego Trip.
不，我对这没有兴趣
No, I'm not interested in that.
你会喜欢它的，道格
You're gonna love this, Doug.
我们提供你以不同的身份去旅行
We offer you a choice of alternate identities during your trip.
想想看，干么以观光客的身份到火星去? 你可以花花公子的身份去
I mean, face it. Why go to Mars as a tourist when you can go as a playboy...
或是著名的运动员，或…
or a famous jock or--
“秘密情报员”
''Secret agent.''
这要多少钱？
How much is that?
让我来对你详细解说一下，你是个第一流的情报员 乔装卧底执行你最重要的任务
Let me tantalize you. You're a top operative, back under deep cover on your most important mission.
黑白两道的人马都在追杀你
People are trying to kill you, left and right.
美丽的，富异国情调的女人
You meet this beautiful, exotic woman.
说下去
Go on.
我不想破坏你到时候享受的乐趣
I don't wanna spoil it for you, Doug...
但我向你保证，在旅程结束时
but you wrest the shore, by the time the trip is over...
你将获得美人的芳心，杀光坏人 拯救整个星球！
you get the girl, kill the bad guys and save the entire planet.
你说说看
Now, you tell me.
这不值得花三百个信用单位吗?
Isn't that worth a measly 300 credits?
- 这是你的第一次旅行？ - 嗯
- It this your first trip? - Um-Huh
别担心，咱们这里很少会出差错的
Well, don't worry. Things hardly ever fuck up around here.
晚安，道格
Good evening... Doug.
- 我是楼大夫 - 幸会
- I'm Dr. Lull. - Nice to meet you.
厄尼，连结第62B及37号的细胞问质
Ernie, patch in matrix 62-B-37.
还有，你想增加些外星怪物吗?
And, would you like us to integrate some alien stuff?
好啊，有何不可?
Sure. Why not?
双头怪物？
Two-headed monsters?
你从来不看新闻吗？
Don't you keep up with the news?
- 我们现在研究外星人的史前古迹 - 看起来真古怪
- We're doing alien artifacts now. - It's wild.
是啊，它们有数百万年的历史
Yeah, they date back a million years.
- 厄尼？ - 这玩意是新的
- Ernie? - That's a new one.
结婚很久了?
- Blue sky on Mars. - Been married long?
- 八年了 - 噢，我明白了
- Eight years. - Oh, I see.
背着老婆出来找些刺激?
Slipping away for a little hanky-panky.
- 不完全是，我一直对火星感兴趣 - 系统运行
- Not really. I've always been fascinated with Mars. - All systems go.
我们可以开始了
Number seven.
准备进入梦乡了？
Ready for dreamland?
首先，我要问你几个问题 如此我们才能适当调整自我之旅
I'll be asking you some questions, Doug, so we can fine-tune the Ego program.
你若能老实回答 你的旅程就会更加偷快
You answer honestly, you'll enjoy yourself whole a lot more.
- 你的性活动倾向是什么? - 异性
- Your sexual orientation. - Hetero.
好，你喜欢什么样的女人?
How do you like your women?
金发的？褐发的？红发的？
Blonde? Brunette? Redhead?
褐发的
Brunette.
苗条的运动员型？肉感型？
Slim. Athletic. Voluptuous.
运动员型
Athletic.
端庄型？侵略型？轻佻型？
Demure. Aggressive. Sleazy.
老实回答
Be honest.
轻佻型…
Sleazy.
端庄型…
Demure.
- 41A，厄尼
- 41A, Ernie.
老天，他将度过一段狂野的时光？
Oh, boy, is he gonna have a wild time?
- 他会不想回来？ - 这是一定的
- Is he not gonna want to come back? - Oh, that's for sure.
那么...
So...
你说呢？
what do you say?
我难以决定，连个纪念品也没有
I'm not so sure, and I don't get a souvenir.
也不尽然，你只要加些额外费用 我们就提供Ｔ恤，以及你在观光点拍的照片
Not true. For just a few more credits, we supply T-shirts, snapshots of you at the site...
甚至信件…
and even letters from the...
- 什么事？ - 你最好快来这边一下
- What is it? - You'd better get down here.
我正在和一个重要客户谈生意
Look, I am with a very important client.
看来咱们又碰上另一个精神分裂栓患者
It looks like we got another schizoid embolism.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
麦克连先生?
Uh, Mr. McClane?
鲍伯，出了什么事？
Bob! What's wrong?
别让她走掉！
Don't let her leave!
你们死定了！你们每一个！
Get off!
你们暴露了我的身份！
You blew my cover!
你连个简单的植入手术都做不好
You can't do a simple goddamn double implant?
不是我的错，他的记忆有问题
Not my fault. We hit a memory cap.
他们随时会到 他们会杀了你们！
They'll be here at any minute! They'll kill you all!
- 他在说些什么？ - 放开我！
- What is he talking about? - Let me go!
魁德先生，试着冷静下来！
Mr. Quaid, try to calm down!
我的名字不叫魁德
My name is not Quaid.
- 让我走，快替我松绑！ - 厄尼，抓住他的腿！
- Let me go! Untie me now! - Ernie, grab his leg!
- 快拉住他！ - 放开我！
- Hold him down! - Let me go!
你没事吧？
Are you all right?
听我说 他一直不停地说着火星的事
Listen to me. he's been going on and on about Mars.
- 他真的到过那里！ - 用你的脑袋想想，你这笨女人！
- He has really been there. - Use your head, you dumb bitch.
他刚刚的表现 正是自我旅行中的情报员角色！
He's just acting out the 'secret agent' portion of his ego trip.
- 这恐怕是不可能的 - 为什么？
- I'm afraid that's not possible. - Why not?
因为我们根本还没将记忆植入！
Because we haven't implanted it yet.
惨了，这下可惨了！
Oh, shit.
这正是我要告诉你的 有人洗掉了他的记忆！
I've been trying to tell you, someone has erased his memory.
对不起
Excuse me.
你是说“某人”？
'Someone'?
我们在谈论该死的情报机构
We're talking about the fucking Agency.
- 闭嘴！ - 鲍伯，那个客户走了
- Shut up! - Bob, the client's gone.
好，好，听我说，咱们就这么办 我们将他所有关于瑞可的记忆通通洗掉
Ok, all right. Look, here's what we're gonna do. Renata, cover up any memory he's got of us or Rekall.
我尽力而为，他的记忆乱成一团
I'll do what I can. It's pretty messy in there.
厄尼，把他搬下去送上出租车 蒂凡霓，你帮他
Ernie, dump him in a cab, around the corner. Tiffany, you help him.
我要毁掉他的资料，退回他的钱
I'm gonna destroy his file and refund his money.
如果有人找上门来 就说我们从没听过道格?魁德
And if anybody comes asking, we never even heard of Douglas Quaid.
我在哪里？
Where am I?
你在一辆钱宁出租车上
You're in a Johnnycab.
我是说，我怎么会在这里?
I mean what am I doing here?
对不起 你能换个方式问这问题吗？
I'm sorry. Would you please rephrase the question?
我怎么会坐上这辆出租车？
How did I get in this taxi?
车门打开，你就上了车
The door opened, you got in.
累了一天，是吧?
Hell of a day, isn't it?
- 这里可以吧？ - 停在这边
- This okay? - Right here.
- 多谢你搭乘钱宁出租车 - 谢谢你
- Thank you for taking Johnnycab. - Thank you.
希望你满意我们的服务
Hope you enjoyed the ride.
嗨，魁德！
Hey, Quaid.
- 哈利? - 你的火星之旅如何？
- Harry. - How was your trip to Mars?
- 什么旅行？ - 你到瑞可公司去，还记得吧？
- What trip? - You went to Rekall. Remember?
- 我有吗？ - 是的，你去了
- I did? - Yeah, you did.
- 我叫你别去，但你偏要去 - 你是谁？我爸爸？
- I told you not to, but you went in anyway. - What are you, my father?
- 来吧，我请你喝一杯 - 听着，我已晚到家了，谢谢你。不过...
- Come on, I'll buy you a drink. - Listen. I'm already late, thank you very much. But...
好，带上他...快点
Okay, bring him-- come on, move it!
咱们这就去喝一杯。快！
Let's go get that drink. move it!
这到底是怎么回事？ 我到底做错了什么？
What is going on? what the fuck did I do wrong?
- 告诉我啊！ - 你乱说话！魁德，你乱说关于火星的事！
- Tell me! - You blabbed, Quaid, you blabbed about Mars!
你疯了吗？ 我对火星一无所知啊？
Are you crazy? I don't even know anything about Mars!
你该听我的话，魁德 我试着让你别惹上麻烦
You should've listened to me, Quaid. I was there to keep you out of trouble.
哈利，你这么做可就错了 你将我误认为某个人
Hey, you're making a big mistake. you got me mixed up with somebody else.
不对，兄弟 是你误认自己是某人
Uh-uh, pal. You got yourself mixed up with somebody--
抛，发球
And pivot... and serve...
收拍，抽球
and shift... and stroke...
很好，完美的动做
Very good. perfect form.
亲爱的
Hi, honey.
- 你在干什么? - 刚刚有几个人想杀我
- What are you doing? - Some men just tried to kill me.
抢匪？你没事吧？
Muggers? Are you all right?
不，他们是间谍之类的
No, they were spies or something.
还有我的同事哈利，他… 快蹲下！
And Harry, from work, he was the-- get down!
- 我的同事哈利，他是带头大哥 - 冷静下来，道格，好吗?
- Harry was the boss. - Take it easy, Doug, okay?
- 把事情的经过详细地告诉我。为何会有间谍想要杀你? - 我不知道
- Tell me exactly what happened. Why would spies wanna kill you? - I don't know.
- 但和火星有关 - 火星？你甚至没到过火星啊！
- But it had something to do with Mars. - Mars? You haven't even been to Mars.
我知道这听来很荒唐 但我今天去了那瑞可公司…
I know, it sounds crazy, but I went to this Rekall place after work--
- 你跑去找那些脑科杀手? - 先让我把话说完
- You went to those brain butchers? - Let me finish.
- 他们把你怎么了？告诉我 - 我到火星旅游了一次。结果…
- What did they do to you, tell me? - I got a trip to Mars. And.. so what happened was
别管瑞可的事行不行？ 那些人想杀我啊！
Forget about Rekall, will you? These guys were going to kill me.
- 道格，没有人想杀你 - 他们想杀我
- Doug, nobody tried to kill you. - They did.
但我杀了他们！
But I killed them.
听我说，亲爱的… 那些瑞可的混蛋弄坏了你的脑袋
Listen to me, sweetheart. Those assholes at Rekall have fucked up your mind.
你开始产生偏执的幻想
You're having paranoid delusions.
你说这也是幻想吗？
You call this a delusion?
- 道格，我要打电话叫医生来 - 不，别打电话给任何人！
- Doug, I'm gonna call a doctor. - Don't. Don't call anybody.
罗莉，快走，离开这里！
Lori, go! Get out!
你为什么要这么做？罗莉
Why are you doing this, Lori?
说！我叫你说！
Talk!
- 我不是你太太 - 你不是才怪
- I'm not your wife. - The hell you're not.
我发誓我六个礼拜以前没见过你
I swear to God I never saw you before six weeks ago.
我们的婚姻只是植入的记忆
Our marriage is just a memory implant.
你认为我是个笨蛋？ 我记得我们的婚礼
You think I'm stupid? I remember our wedding.
那是情报局植入的记忆
It was an implant by the Agency.
- 恋爱？ - 植入的
- Falling in love. - Implanted.
我们的朋友？我的工作？八年在一起的时光？ 难道这些也全是植入的记忆?
Our friends, my job, 8 years together. Suppose all of these was implanted, too?
工作是真的 是情报局替你安排的
The job's real. The Agency set it up.
狗屁！
Bullshit.
他们抹掉你的身份 植入一个新的
They erased your identity and implanted a new one.
我被安排来当你的太太 以便就近监视，确定你的记忆被彻底洗干净
I was written in as your wife so that I could watch you and make sure the erasure took.
抱歉，魁德
Sorry, Quaid.
你这一生只是一场梦
Your whole life is just a dream.
好，那么…如果我不是我… 那么我又是谁？
Okay, then if I'm not me, who the hell am I?
问倒我了
Beats me.
我只是奉命派来这里工作
I just work here.
道格，我要你知道一件事
Doug, there's something I want you to know.
你是我出过的任务中最棒的 我是说真的
You were the best assignment I ever had. Really.
我感到很荣幸
I'm honored.
你真的不要再来一次吗? 念夜往日的情份上…
You sure you don't want to, just for old times' sake?
来吧，如果你不信任我 可以把我绑起来
Come on, if you don't trust me, you can tie me up.
- 我不晓得你原来这么变态 - 或许你也该知道这点了
- I didn't know you were so kinky. - Maybe it's time you found out.
好聪明的女孩
Clever girl.
你该不会真的开枪吧？道格 咱们毕竟夫妻一场啊！
You wouldn't shoot me, will you? Doug. after all we've been through.
是的，的确有些偷快的时光…
Some of it was fun.
很高兴认识你
Nice knowing you.
别碰她
Don't touch her.
屋里没人
Nobody here.
- 你没事吧 - 我想我是坏了大事
- Are you okay? - I guess I blew it.
- 他想起了什么？ - 到目前为止什么也没有
- What does he remember? - Nothing, so far.
我追踪到他了
I've got him.
糟糕，他朝地下铁的方向去了 咱们追上去 咱们走！
Shit! He's going for the subway. Let's get him. Go.
收拾行李离开这里
Pack your stuff and get outta here.
如果他们把他抓回来呢?
What if they bring him back?
这是不可能的
Not a chance.
地下铁，快！
Subway! Go!
抓住他 他身上有枪！
Get him! he's got a gun!
- 堵住他的去路，那边！ - 站住！别动！
- Cut him off! That way! - Over there!
Hold it!
自动扶梯
The escalator.
你们四个上去！你跟我来！
You four go up. you come with me.
闪开！闪开！
Get out of the way!
Get out of the way! Move!
站台！
The platform!
- 哪边？ - 右边！
- Which way? - To the right.
巴科，明日的燃料，明日的价格
Botco. tomorrow's fuels, tomorrow's prices.
别满足于苍白的回忆 别被骗去植入假记忆
Don't settle for pale memories. Don't go for fake implants.
以传统方式享受一次美好的假期
Experience space travel the old-fashioned way...
人人享受得起！
on a real, live holiday you can afford.
我要那王八蛋死！
I want that fucker dead.
我能体会你的心情 我也不愿意让魁德这种人玩我的老婆
I don't blame you, man. I wouldn't want a guy like Quaid porking my old lady.
- 你是说她喜欢这么做？ - 不，我认为她痛恨和他在一起的每一刻
- You're saying she likes it? - No, I'm sure she hated every minute of it.
请接科海根先生的传真电话
Six-beta-nine, we have a live transmission from Mr. Cohaagen. 6B9，6B9
- 我是瑞克特，传过来 - 请讲，科海根先生
- Richter here. Patch it through. - You're a go, Mr. Cohaagen.
- 这到底是怎么一回事？ - 我正在追杀一个叛徒，长官
- What is the fuck is going on down there? - I'm trying to neutralize a traitor, sir.
如果我要他死，你这白痴 就不会将他丢在地球上！
If I wanted him dead, you moron. I would have done it on earth.
我们不能让他到处跑 他知道太多的秘密
We can't let him run around. He knows too much.
罗莉说他什么也不记得
Lori says he can't remember jackshit.
现在是如此 一小时后他将完全恢复记忆
That's an hour, an hour he could have total recall.
给我听着，瑞克特 我要你将魁德活着送回来，重新植入记忆
Listen to me, Richter. I want Quaid delivered alive for reimplantation.
你听清楚了没？
Have you got that?
我要他回去跟罗莉重聚
I want him back in place with Lori.
你听见了没?
Did you hear me?
你说什么?长官，我听不见
What was that, sir? I couldn't hear you.
你在干什么? 我追踪到梅琳娜
What are you doing? I got Quaid again.
转到另一个频道，长官 有太阳黑子干扰
Switching to another channel, sir. I've got sunspots.
- 给我回电话！给我回电话！ - 我无法接收到你了
- Call him back! - I'm losing you.
- 他在哪？ - 加星利区，第二层
- Where is he? - Second level, galleria.
你该在火星上就把魁德干掉的
We should've killed Quaid on Mars.
“丽池大饭店”
- 信号的接收状况呢？ - 好极了
- How are we doing? - Fine.
我现在将它放大
Zooming in.
锁定住他了！
We got him!
如果你想活命，就别挂断
If you want to live, don't hang up.
- 你想怎样！ - 你身上有追踪器
- What do you want? - I've got your bug.
他们在三分钟后就要破门而入 除非你照我的话去做
They'll be bust in your door in three minutes unless you do exactly as l say.
不必找了，追踪器在你的头里
Don't bother searching. the bug's in your skull.
- 你是谁？ - 别管我是谁
- Who are you? - Never mind.
找条湿毛巾包在你的头上 这可以减弱讯号
Wet a towel and wrap it around your head. that'll muffle the signal.
- 你是如何找到我的？ - 我奉劝你最好快点照办
- How'd you find me? - I'd advise you to hurry.
这可让你争取一些时间 他们将无法锁定你
This'll buy you some time. they won't be able to pinpoint you.
- 该死！ - 怎么回事？
- Shit! - What?
- 我追丢他了 - 再给我找！
- I lost him. - Well, find him!
好的
Yeah, right.
快点，你看来很正点
Come on, hurry up. You look beautiful.
现在到窗口去 快去
Now go to the window. go.
- 看得见我吗？ - 嗯
- Can you see me down here? - Um-hum.
- 这是你交给我的那口箱子 - 我交给你的？
- This is the suitcase you gave me. - I gave you?
我把它放在这里 你到下面来拿，然后继续走
I'm gonna set it here. You come and get it, keep moving.
- 慢着，等一下！ - 什么事?
- Wait. Wait. - What?
- 你是谁? - 我是你在火星情报局时的同事
- Who are you? - We were buddies in the Agency back on Mars.
你说过你若是失踪的话就来找你 所以我来了，再见
You asked me, if you disappeared, to come and find you, so here I am. Good-bye.
我在火星上时是做什么?
What was I doing on Mars?
对不起，太太，这是我的
Excuse me, Mam, but this is mine.
- 上面又没写你的名字！ - 是人家留给我的
- I don't see your name on it. - Someone left it for me.
- 去找你自己的箱子！ - 对不起，太太，我真的需要它
- Find your own bag. - Excuse me, Mam, but I need it!
操你的，你这王八蛋！
Fuck you, you asshole!
那狗娘养的一定就在这附近
Son of a bitch's gotta be around here somewhere.
那边那家伙！
That guy there.
哈罗，我是钱宁出租车 今晚上哪去?
Hello, I'm Johnnycab. where can l take you tonight?
开车！开车！
Drive. Drive!
- 麻烦你重复一下这地址好吗? - 上哪去都行，开车就是了！
- Would you please repeat the destination? - Anywhere! Just go! Go!
请说出一个街名和号码
Please state the street and number.
妈的！妈的！
Shit. Shit!
我没听过这个地址 能否请你重复…
I'm not familiar with that address. would you please repeat--
系上你的安全带
Fasten your seat belt!
车资一共是18个信用单位
The fare is 18 credits, please.
去告我好了，笨蛋
Sue me, dickhead.
希望你满意我们的服务！
We hope you enjoyed the ride.
你好，陌生人，我是豪瑟
Howdy, stranger. this is Hauser.
如果事情出了差错 我如今就得对着自己说话
If things have gone wrong, I'm talking to myself...
而你则得在头上包着湿毛巾
and you've got a wet towel wrapped around your head.
不管你叫什么名字 下面这事实包准叫你大吃一惊
Whatever your name is, get ready for the big surprise.
你并不是你 你其实是我
You are not you. you are me.
真的?
No shit.
6B9，6B9，请回答
Six-beta-nine, six-beta-nine, come in.
你找到他了?
Did you find him?
我们扫瞄到废弃的水泥工厂 发生了一场爆炸
We picked up an explosion at the old cement factory.
- 派两组人过去，咱们在那里碰头 - 知道了
- Send two units. We'll meet you there. - Roger
我这辈子都在火星情报部工作
All my life I've worked for Mars Intelligence.
替科海根做了许多伤天害理的事
I did Cohaagen's dirty work.
但几个礼拜前我遇到一个人，一个女人
But a few weeks ago I met somebody, a woman.
她让我觉悟到一些事
And I learned a few things.
比方说，我是在助盗为虐
Like, I've been playing for the wrong team.
我现在能做的 就是好好弥补一下过去的罪擎
All I can do now is try to make up for it.
要知道，这个脑袋里装的东西 可以让科海根死得很惨
See, there's enough shit in here to fuck Cohaagen good.
不幸的是，如果你听到这段话 就表示他已经先一步整倒了我
Unfortunately, if you're listening to this, that means he has got to me first.
最困难的部份就在此，兄弟
And here comes the hard part, old buddy.
从现在起全得靠你了
Now it is all up to you.
真是太好了
Great.
- 你们找到了什么？ - 车上没有人
- What have we got? - Nothing here.
- 他已经走了 - 我抓到前方有微弱的讯号
- He's gone. - I got a weak signal over there.
散开，把他找出来
Split up. Find him.
首先，将你头里的追踪器取出来
First let's get rid of that bug in your head.
将这东西从箱子里拿出来 然接插进你的鼻子里
Take this thing out of the case and stick it up your nose.
别担心，它是自动导向的
Don't worry. It's self-guiding.
用力插进去就行了
Just shove real hard.
当你听到一个碎裂声，那就是了
When you hear a crunches, you're there.
将它拉出来
Just pull it out.
但得小心，那也是我的脑袋
Be careful. It's my head too.
我锁定住他了！
I've got a lock.
在上面 咱们上！
Up. Let's go.
我的计划是这样的…
Now, this is the plan.
你到火星上去
Get your ass to Mars...
然后到希尔顿饭店出示一份 布鲁贝克的证件给柜台接待员
then go to the Hilton and flash the Brubaker I.D. at the desk.
如此就行了
That's all does to it.
照我的话去做，咱们两个就可以让那个狗杂种 得到应有的制裁。我全靠你了，兄弟
Just do what I tell you. If we can nail this son of a bitch who fucked you and me.  I'm counting on you, Buddy.
可别让我失望
Don't let me down.
正前方
Straight ahead.
在这里面
In there.
那边
There!
给我！
Give me that.
他妈的！
Shit.
上你妈的火星去... 上你妈的火星去...
Get your ass to Mars-- get your ass to Mars--
欢迎光临火星联邦自治区
Welcome to the Mars Federal Colony.
为了各位的健康和舒适 我们建造了圆顶
For your safety and comfort, domes have been installed...
以隔绝外界的真空环境
to protect you from the vacuum outside.
请不要碰触外侧的窗户或气闸
Please do not touch exterior windows or air locks.
由于本地的空气供应量极为有限 此地全面禁止吸烟…
And since the air volume is limited. No smoking is allowed anywhere in the colony.
下一个！
Next.
谢谢各位 祝你们在火星的停留期间偷快
Thank you, and enjoy your stay on Mars.
护照呢?
Passport.
- 快点，闪一边去 - 让路！
- Get out of the way. - Make way!
退后！
Stand back.
科海根先生要见你，马上！
Mr. Cohaagen wants to see you right away.
有魁德的消息吗？
Any news of Quaid?
- 自从你追丢他之后就没有了 - 讲话当心点！上尉 - 我们有车送你到港口
- Not since you lost him. - Watch your mouth, Captain. - We've got a car to take you from the port.
- 你打算在火星上停留多久？ - 两个礼拜
- How long do you plan to stay? - Two weeks.
看看那上面写的 “寡头万岁”
Look at that shit.
- 这他妈的又是什么？ - 火星的人民爱戴寡头
- What the hell's this? - The Martians love Kuato.
他们以为他是华盛顿再世
They think he's fuckin' George Washington.
宰了这混蛋
Kill the bastard.
没人知道他到底是谁
Nobody knows who he is.
你有携带任何水果或蔬菜吗?
Have you brought any fruits  or vegetables onto the planet?
两个礼拜
Two weeks.
你说什么？
Excuse me?
两个礼拜
Two weeks.
那不只是普通的涂鸦
It's not just graffiti.
叛军咋晚攻占了炼制厂
The rebels took over the refinery last night.
所有的Ｔ矿都无法输出
No terbinium is going out.
情况还会更严重
And it gets worse.
魁德
Quaid.
- 那就是魁德！ - 哪里？
- That's Quaid! - Where?
那个女人，把他抓起来！ 我是说“她”！
The woman! get him-- her!
逮捕那女人！
Arrest that woman!
抓住那女人！拦住她！
Get that woman! Grab her!
接住！
Catch!
准备大吃一惊吧！
Get ready for a surprise!
- 把这该死的门打开！ - 我办不到
- Open the goddamn door! - I can't!
把它打开！
Open it!
这些门和气闸是连接在一起的！
They're all connected!
- 真可怕 - 而且前几天科海根又提高空气的价格
- That's terrible. - And a few days ago Cohaagen raised the price of air.
- 又一次？ - 地球上的人根本不管我们死活
- Again? - Nobody on Earth gives a damn what happens up here.
他们只要Ｔ矿 好能够去打他们那无聊的战争
And they just want terbinium so they can fight the stupid war.
对不起，那是什么？
Excuse me. What's that?
你是指那金字塔矿场？
You mean the Pyramid Mine?
我在那里工作过 直到他们在里面发现那些外星人留下来的东西
I used to work there until they found that alien shit inside.
这不是传闻而已吗？
Well, that's a rumor, isn't it?
你认为如此？
Think so?
科海根先生
Mr. Cohaagen.
你有事找我？长官
You wanted to see me, sir?
瑞克特
Richter...
你知道我为何如此快乐吗？
do you know why I'm such a happy person?
不知道，长官
No, sir.
因为我有全太阳系最棒的工作
Because I've got the greatest job in the solar system.
只要Ｔ矿一直生产下去 我就能做任何我想做的事
As long as the terbinium keeps flowing, I can do anything I want.
任何事
Anything.
事实上…
In fact.,
我唯一担心的事只是 若有那么一天
The only thing I ever worried about is that one day...
叛军获得了胜利
if the rebels win...
这一切就可能随之结束...
it all might end...
而你却要造成这种结果！
and you're fucking making it happen!
首先你企图杀魁德 然后你又让他逃掉！
First you trying kill Quaid, then you let him get away.
他有我们的人暗中帮助，长官
He had help from our side, sir.
这我知道
I know that.
- 但我以为… - 谁叫你想？
- But I thought-- - Who told you to think?
我可没给你足够的数据来思考！
I don't give you  enough information to think.
你只要奉令行事就行了！
You do what you're told. that's what you do.
是，长官
Yes, sir.
现在…咱们开始来谈正事
Now, let's get down to business.
我们面临一个难缠的局面
We've got a tricky situation here.
寡头要魁德脑袋里所知道的东西
Kuato wants what's in Quaid's head.
而且他也有可能得到 因为传闻他有心电感应的能力
And he might be able to get it. cause they say he's psychic.
而我已想出一个计划来阻止他成功
And I have a plan to keep this from happening.
你认为你这回可以好好合作吗?
Do you think you could play along?
- 是的，长官 - 好极了
- Yes, sir. - Great.
否则，我就会取你的狗命！
Cause otherwise, I'll erase your ass.
出租车？你要坐出租车吗？ 先生，我的车上有杂志，音乐，威土忌
Taxi? You need a taxi? Sir, I got magazines, music, whisky.
兄弟，要搭出租车吗？来吧
You need a cab, Man? Come on!
“希尔顿饭店”
午安，我能效劳吗？
Afternoon! Can I help you?
是的，麻烦你给我一个房间
Yes, I would like a room, please.
欢迎再次光临，布鲁贝克先生 你要同一间套房？
Nice to have you back, Mr. Brubaker. would you like the same suite?
当然
Definitely.
你似乎有东西放在保管箱里
Seemed you've left something in our safe.
能否麻烦你将它拿来给我？
Could you get it?
我们要核对身份
Identification?
- 我这就去拿你房间的钥匙 - 谢谢
- I'll go and code your room key. - Thank you.
“终极乐园”
“享受好时光，请找梅琳娜”
- 钥匙在这里，布鲁贝克先生。西大楼的610号房 - 谢谢
- There you go, Mr Brubaker. Suite 610 in the east wing. - Thank you.
- 我能借用你的笔吗? - 当然
- Could I borrow your pen, please? - Certainly.
谢谢你
Thank you.
兄弟，坐出租车？
Hey, man, you need a cab?
- 这一辆的服务会比你差吗？ - 他可没有要养五个孩子啊！
- What's wrong with this one? - He ain't got five kids to feed.
- 你的车在哪？ - 就在那边，兄弟
- Where's yours? - Right over there, Man.
王八蛋，这是我的客人啊！
Hey, asshole! that's my fare!
一边凉快去！
Eat this!
班尼，你这该死的…
Damn you, Benny!
欢迎光临火星，兄弟
Welcome to Mars, man!
- 刚刚那是什么？意外事件？ - 是反抗军干的
- What the hell was that, an accident? - That's the rebels, man.
咱们快离开此地吧！
Let's get outta here...
否则待会就会被捕
before they arrest us!
反叛军要的是什么？
What do the rebels want?
和往常一样，更多的钱，更多自由，更多空气
All the usual. more money, more freedom, more air.
上哪去?
So, where to?
终极乐园
Last Resort.
才刚到就迫不急待了？
You're getting off to an early start.
- 第一回来火星？ - 是的
- First time on Mars? - Yes.
事实上…不是
Well, actually, no.
也可说是
Well, sort of.
老天，连自己是否来过火星都弄不清楚
Damn, the man don't even know whether he's been to Mars or not.
这就是了！维纳斯城
Voila. Venusville.
看到中意的货色没？
Hey, you see anything you like?
车子只能开到此 我们接下来最好用走的
Well, this is the end of the line. we'd better walk from here.
我带你到那地方去
I'll show you the way.
- 想知道你的未来吗？ - 过去呢?
- Do you wanna know the future? - What about the past?
来吧，就在转角的地方 就在这巷子里
Come on, it's around the corner, right down this alley.
他们这里什么都有
They got everything.
想爽一下吗？不错吧？
Not bad, huh?
看手相?读你的心思? 你的欲念？你心里的秘密？
Read your palm? Your mind? Your aura? probe the secrets of your heart?
- 我打赌我猜得出你的生日 - 你说呢？
- I bet I can guess your birthday. - What is it?
- 你是金牛座的，对吧 - 你怎么猜到的？
- You're a Taurus, right? - How did you guess?
- 告诉我，所有的通灵人都是… - 变种？
- Tell me something, are all the psychics-- - Freaks?
全是变种。是这一带的特产
Afraid so. It goes with the territory.
- 他们怎么会变成这样 - 廉价的圆顶，又没空气来挡有害的射线
- What happened to them? - Cheap domes, and no air to clean up the rays.
好，咱们到了，终极乐园 你真的要在这间玩吗？兄弟
So, this is it. The Last Resort. you sure you want to go in here?
- 有何不可？ - 我认识另外一家更好的
- Why not? - I know this much better place down the street.
女孩子比较干净，酒也不掺水
The girls are cleaner, the liquor ain't watered down--
是啊，你还可以拿到回扣
Sure, and you get kickbacks.
兄弟，我有五个孩子要养啊！
Hey, man, I got five kids to feed.
带他们去看牙医吧！
Take them to the dentist.
谢了，先生，听我说，我在外面等你
Thanks, mister! Hey, mister, I'll be waiting for you.
你慢慢玩好了 我叫班尼，班尼！
Take your time. Benny's the name. Benny!
- 要什么？ - 我找梅琳娜
- What do you want? - I'm looking for Melina.
她现在很忙
She's busy.
找马丽好了，她有空(免费)
But Mary here, she's free.
不是免费，亲爱的，而是…
Well, not free, honey, but...
有空
available. Hahaha.
谢谢，我还是等梅琳娜好了
Thanks. I'll wait for Melina.
地球无赖！
Earth slime.
问题是，梅琳娜对客人是很挑的
Thing is, friend, mel's real picky.
她一向只招待熟客人
She kinds sticks to her regulars.
她会喜欢我的
She'll like me.
梅琳娜！
Mel! Hey, Mel!
哈罗，豪瑟
Hello, Hauser.
看得出你仍是全身鼓胀如昔
Still bulging, I see.
- 近来都喂养什么? - 金发女郎
- What have you been feeding this thing? - Blondes.
那我想它八成没吃饱了？
I think it's still hungry.
你还有脸跑来这里啊？豪瑟
You got a lot of nerve showing your face around here, Hauser.
这句话应该是我说的才对
Look who's talking.
东尼，别再烦他了
Hey, Tony, give the big guy a break.
放轻松点，如此才活得久
Relax. You'll live longer.
来吧！
Come on.
- 亲爱的，替我去招待东尼好吗？ - 没问题
- Honey, take care of Tony, will you? - No problem.
如果你应付不了这一个 就喊我一声
If you need any help with this one, give me a holler.
你这狗娘养的！
You son of a bitch.
你还活着？ 我都以为你被科海根折磨死了
You're alive? I thought that Cohaagen tortured you to death.
我想他大概没这么做吧
Well, I guess he didn't.
而你却无法传个口信给我？ 你难道都没关心过我的死活?
And you couldn't get me a message? You never even wondered what happened to me?
豪瑟，谢天谢地，你还活着
Hauser! Hauser, thank God you're alive.
梅琳…梅琳娜 梅琳娜，梅琳娜！
Melin-- Melina. Melina.
- 我有话要告诉你 - 什么事？
- I have to tell you something. - What?
- 我已经不记得你了 - 你在胡说些什么？
- I don't remember you. - What are you talking about?
我不记得你了
I don't remember you.
我不记得我们之间的事 我甚至不记得我自己的过去
I don't remember us. I don't even remember me.
怎么？你得了失忆症？ 你是如何找来这里的？
Oh, what? Did you get amnesia? how did you get here?
- 豪瑟留给我一张字条 - 豪瑟？你就是豪瑟
- Hauser left me a note. - You're Hauser.
已经不是了
Not anymore.
我现在是魁德 道格拉斯?魁德
Now I'm Quaid. Douglas Quaid.
- 豪瑟，你精神错乱了 - 我没有精神错乱。科海根偷了我的记忆
- Hauser, you've lost your mind. - I didn't lose my mind. Cohaagen stole it.
他发现豪瑟企图背叛他 于是将他变成另一个人，变成我
He found out that Hauser switched sides, so he turned him into somebody else: me.
这故事太玄了
This is too weird.
再把我丢在地球上 给我一个老婆和一份烂工作
He dumped me on earth with a wife and a lousy job--
你说你有老婆？ 你他妈的结婚了？
Did you say... Did you say wife? are you fucking married?
- 她其实不是我真正的太太 - 她不是你真正的太太？
- She wasn't really my wife. - Oh, she isn't really your wife?
我可真笨 她是豪瑟的太太？
How stupid of me. she was Hauser's wife?
- 听着，忘了我提到… - 不，一切都别再说了！
- Look, forget that I said wife. - No, let's just forget everything.
- 我受够了你和你那些谎言 - 我为何要骗你？
- I'm sick of hearing your goddamn lies. - Why would I lie to you?
因为你仍在为科海根工作
Because you're still working for Cohaagen.
别胡说了
Don't be ridiculous.
你根本就没爱过我，豪瑟
You never loved me, Hauser.
你只想利用我，好混进去
You just used me to get inside.
混进什么里面
Inside what?
我看你还是走吧
I think you'd better leave.
- 梅琳娜，豪瑟派我来做某件事 - 我可不会上当
- Melina, Hauser sent me to do something. - I'm not falling for it.
他说这脑袋里装的东西足以整垮科海根
He says there's enough in here to nail Cohaagen for good.
- 滚！ - 你得帮我恢复记忆！
- Get out! - You've got to help me remember!
- 我叫你滚！ - 梅琳娜，求求你
- I said, get out! - Melina, please!
有人要杀我啊！
People are trying to kill me.
真的？
Really?
好吧，我这就走
All right, I'm leaving.
宝贝，你让我恨不得能有三只手
Baby, you make me wish I had three hands.
我想你这两只手已经很够用了
Well, I think you're doing just fine with two.
失陪一下，宝贝，咱们待会再聊
Excuse me, baby. we'll pick this up later.
兄弟，你不怎么持久啊！
Hey, that didn't take long.
听着，我问你，你玩过变种妞吗？
Listen, let me ask you a question. did you ever fuck a mutant?
- 送我回饭店去 - 我认识一对变种双胞胎
- Take me to the hotel. - I know these Siamese twins.
保证让你爽歪歪
Man, you won't know if you're coming or going.
今天下午四点半时 我签署一份法令
This afternoon at 4:30 p.m., I signed an order declaring martial law...
批准在火星联邦自治区实施戒严
throughout the Mars Federal Colony.
我将不会再容忍任何 破坏矿物输出的行为
I will not tolerate any further damage to our mineral export operations.
寡头先生和他手下的恐怖份子 必须明白一件事
Mr. Kuato and his terrorists must understand...
他们这种自取毁灭的行为 只会为人民带来苦难和痛苦…
that their self-defeating efforts will only bring misery and suffering to the people...
魁德先生？
Mr. Quaid?
什么事？
What?
我要跟你谈谈 是关于豪瑟先生的事
I need to talk to you about Mr. Hauser.
- 你是谁？ - 瑞可公司的艾吉马大夫
- Who are you? - Dr. Edgemar from Rekall.
- 你是如何找到我的？ - 解释起来有点复杂
- How did you find me? - It's a little difficult to explain.
你能开门吗？ 我没有带武器
Could you open the door? I'm unarmed.
别担心，我是一个人来的 我可以进去吗？
Don't worry. I'm alone. may I come in?
- 你来做什么？ - 你听了后可能会有点难以接受
- What do you want? - This is gonna be very difficult for you to accept, Mr Quaid.
- 我在听 - 你此时恐怕不是真的站在这里
- I'm listening. - I'm afraid you're not really standing here right now.
- 你知道吗？大夫，你差点就骗过我了 - 我可是说正经的
- Hum. You know. Doc, you could fool me. - I'm quite serious.
你不在这里 我也不在
You're not here and neither am I.
这倒新鲜
That's amazing.
- 我们又是在哪？ - 在瑞可公司
- Where are we? - At Rekall.
你被绑在一张手术椅上
You're strapped into an implant chair...
而我则透过精神追踪探针 观察你的情形
and I'm monitoring you from the psychoprobe console.
我明白了，原来我是在做梦
Ah, I get it. I'm dreaming.
而这一切全是贵公司卖给我的 一回刺激的假期的一部份
And all this is a part of the delightful vacation your company has sold me.
不完全是
Not exactly.
你目前所经历的，全是根据我们制作的记忆母带 所自由创造出来的幻象
What you're experiencing is a free-form delusion based on our memory tapes...
你将不断地发展出新的情节
but you're inventing it yourself as you go along.
假设这是我创造出来的幻象 那么又是谁请你来插花的？
Well, if it is my delusion, who the hell invited you?
我被植入这程序 以便发生状况时能加以补救
I've been artificially implanted as an emergency measure.
我不得不告诉你，魁德先生 你在手术中出现精神分裂栓
I'm sorry to tell you this, Mr Quaid, but you've suffered a schizoid embolism.
我们无法让你从幻想中醒来
We can't snap you out of your fantasy...
于是我被派来 看看是否能劝你回到现实世界
and I've been sent in to try to talk you down.
科海根付你多少钱来干这种事？
How much is Cohaagen paying you for this?
你想想看 你的梦是在植入的过程中开始的
Think about it. Your dream started in the middle of the implant procedure.
那以后发生的一切，包括追杀，到达火星
Everything after that-- the chases, the trip to Mars...
住宿于希尔顿饭店， 全是瑞可公司提供你的自我旅行情节
the suite at the Hilton are all elements of your Rekall Holiday and Ego Trip.
你付钱来扮演秘密情报员
You paid to be a secret agent.
狗屁，这不过是巧合罢了
Bullshit. It's coincidence.
那么那个女孩呢？
And what about the girl?
褐发，运动员体型…既放荡又端庄？
Brunette, athletic, sleazy and demure?
完全符合你所指定的特征 这也是巧合吗？
Just as you specified. Is that coincidence?
她是真的存在的 我在去瑞可之前就梦见过她了
Uh. She's real. l dreamt about her before I even went to Rekall.
魁德先生…
Mr. Quaid.
你知道你这逻辑有多荒唐吗？ 你梦见过她，所以她是真的？
Can you hear yourself? she's real because you dreamed her?
- 没错 - 或许这将能使你信服…
- That's right. - Oh, maybe this'll convince you.
你能把门打开吗？
Would you mind opening the door?
- 你去开 - 没有必要动粗
- You open it. - No need to be rude.
我来开好了
I'll do it.
亲爱的？
Sweetheart?
进来吧，魁德太太
Come in, Mrs. Quaid.
- 我猜你此时也不是真的在此了？ - 我在这里...
- What I supposed you're not here either. - I'm here...
在瑞可公司
at Rekall.
我爱你
I love you.
是啊。所以你才会想杀我
Right. That's why you tried to kill me.
不，我绝不会做任何伤害你的事
No. I'd never do anything to hurt you.
我要你回到我的身边
I want you to come back to me.
- 狗屁！ - 什么才是狗屁？魁德先生
- Bullshit. - What's bullshit, Mr. Quaid?
是你的细胞受到精神化学损伤 而引发一连串偏执的幻想？
That you're having a paranoid episode triggered by acute neurochemical trauma?
还是你真的是一个 来自火星的卧底秘密情报员...
Or that you're really an invincible secret agent from Mars...
受到一项星际阴谋的迫害 让你自以为是个...
who's the victim of an interplanetary conspiracy to make him think...
卑微的建筑工人？
he's a lowly construction worker?
别再折磨你自己了，道格
Stop punishing yourself, Doug.
你是个正直的好人 你有个深爱着你的美丽妻子
You're a fine, upstanding man. you have a beautiful wife who loves you.
你还有许多美好的日子要过
Your whole life is ahead of you.
但你得先愿意回到现实的世界
But you've got to want to return to reality.
就算我愿意好了…我又该怎么做？
Let's assume I do, Then what?
- 把这个吞下去 - 这是什么？
- Swallow this. - What is it?
它是一个象征 表示你愿意回到现实的世界
It's a symbol of your desire to return to reality.
在你的梦里，你将睡着
Inside your dream, you'll fall asleep.
好吧，假设你说的全是事实 这一切全是一场梦
All right, let's say you're telling the truth and this is all a dream.
那我大可扣下扳机，反正也不要紧
Then I could pull this trigger and it won't matter.
- 道格，别这么做 - 这对我不会有什么差别，道格
- Doug, don't. - It won't make a slightest difference to me, Doug.
但对你却会有毁灭性的结果 在你的脑海里，我将丧命
But the consequences to you would be devastating. In your mind I'll be dead.
在无人引导你走出的情况下 你将陷入永久的精神错乱
With no one to guide you out, you'll be stuck in permanent psychosis.
道格，让艾吉马大夫帮助你
Doug, let Dr. Edgemar help you.
现实世界的墙将整个倒塌
The walls of reality will come crashing down.
在前一分钟里，你还是拯救叛军的大英雄 但接下来…你又将是科海根的心腹爪牙！
One minute, you will be hero who saved rebel clause. And the next thing you konw,  you'll be Cohaagen's bosom buddy.
你甚至将如你当初所要求的 幻想在太空中发现外星文明
You'll even have fantasies about alien civilizations, as you requested...
但在你终于回到现实世界后 你将被切除前脑！
but in the end, back on earth you'll be lobotomized!
所以还是理智点，道格，把枪放下！
So get a grip on yourself, Doug, and put down that gun!
很好。现在把那粒胶囊放进嘴里
Good. Now take the pill and put it in your mouth.
吞下去！
Swallow it!
吞下去！亲爱的
Go ahead, sweetheart.
看看你干了什么好事！ 看你干了什么好事！
Now you've done it. Now you've done it!
这是回敬你害我跑来火星
That's for making me come to Mars.
你知道我有多痛恨这个烂星球！
You know how much I hate this fucking planet!
把他铐起来
Cuff him.
- 我抓住他了 - 好极了，用服务电梯将他送下来
- I got him. - Good. Bring him down in the service elevator.
我们走
Let's go.
操你的！
Fuck you!
道格
Doug.
亲爱的
Honey...
你不会伤害我，对不对？亲爱的
you wouldn't hurt me, would you, sweetheart?
亲爱的…理智点
Sweetheart, be reasonable.
毕竟…咱们是夫妻啊！
After all, we're married.
现在离婚了
Consider that a divorce.
她就是你的老婆？
That was your wife?
好一个贱人！
What a bitch.
闪一边去！
Hey, get out of the way!
我还以为你不喜欢我
I thought you didn't like me.
如果科海根要杀你，你就应该没问题
If Cohaagen wants you dead, you might be okay.
- 找到了 - 那么你是回来向我道歉了？
- Got it. - So you've come back to apologize.
寡头要见你
Kuato wants to see you.
快走！
Come on.
- 现在怎么办？ - 跳！
- Now what? - Jump!
- 不！别开枪！ 你会把圆顶打破的！
No! Don't do it! you'll crack the fucking dome!
如果你这么做，咱们全都会没命 圆顶会破裂的！
What are you trying to do, kill us? The dome will crack!
走开！
Move!
出租车！
Taxi!
梅琳娜！梅琳娜！
Melina! Melina!
- 要坐车吗？ - 快，到终极乐园
- Need a ride? - Last Resort, quick!
你们这些人尽在兜圈子
You guys are going in circles.
我的天！
Jesus!
快点！你开车！
Come on! You drive!
你们是惹上了什么麻烦？
You guys are in trouble?
开车！开车！
Go! Go!
- 你是想害死我？兄弟 - 闭嘴，开你的车就行了！
- What are you trying to do to me, Man? - Shut up and drive!
我还有五个孩子要养啊！
Hey, I got five kids to feed!
糟了！
Shit!
车失灵了！
No brakes!
你这个白痴！
You idiot!
你在干什么啊？
What the hell are you doing?
我的天，现在他们也要杀我了！
Christ! Now they're after me!
把枪给我
Give me that!
滚一边去！
Get out of the way!
东尼！
Tony!
别挡路！ 快来！
Get out of the way! come on!
快！快！
Come on! Come on!
谢谢你，东尼
Thank you, Tony.
你要…乐一下吗？
Hey, you wanna, have some fun?
他们在哪里？
Where are they?
你在说什么啊？我不知道
What are you talking about? I don't know.
或许你知道
Maybe you know.
把他们都宰了！
Kill them all!
桑卜琳娜！
Thumbelina!
瑞克特！
Richter!
- 科海根打电话找你 - 我是瑞克特
- A call from Cohaagen! - Richter here.
- 我们压制住他们了 - 停止战斗，将人员撤出
- We've got them pinned down. - Stop fighting and pull out.
但他们藏匿魁德，还保护他
But they've got Quaid. they're protecting him.
好极了 立刻撤出G区
Perfect. get out of Sector G now.
别想
Don't think.
- 照办就是了！ - 是，长官
- Do it! - Yes, sir.
将人员撤回！
Pull'em out.
所有人员撤退！
Everybody, pull out!
快！
Move!
- 科海根要将这一区封死！ - 快来！班尼
- Cohaagen's sealing off the area! - Come on, Benny!
第一代的移民埋骨于此
The first settlers are buried here.
他们苦干到死 但财富却全落到科海根手里
They worked themselves to death, but cohaagen ended up with all the money.
他替他们建廉价的圆顶 让他们的后代变成奇形人
He built cheap domes and watched the kids turn into freaks.
我见过他们了
I saw them.
如果你想呼吸，还得跟他买空气
And if you want to breathe, you have to buy his air.
或许你能改变这一切
Maybe you can change all that.
我想我的爷爷可能也埋在这里
Hey, I think my grandpa might be here.
我能做什么？
So what can I do?
寡头将让你想起 当你还是豪瑟时所知道的事
Kuato's gonna make you remember some things you knew when you were Hauser.
- 比方说什么？ - 各种的事
- Like what? - All sorts of things.
- 比方说，或许你会想起你曾爱过我 - 这倒不需要寡头的帮忙
- Like maybe you'll remember you loved me. - I don't need Kuato for that.
从什么时候开始的？
Since when?
别动！
Freeze!
来吧，梅琳娜
Come on, Melina.
寡头在等了
Kuato's waiting.
我找不到我的爷爷，但是...
Hey, I didn't find Grandpa, but--
我的妈呀！
Oh, shit.
- 这家伙是谁？ - 是他帮助我们逃走的
- Who's this? - He helped us get away.
你们无须担心我，兄弟 我是站在你们这边的
Hey, don't worry about me, man. I'm on your side.
原来你是个变种人，是吧?
You're a mutant, huh?
好吧，我们走
All right, let's go.
- 你有试过将门炸开吗？ - 你在这里等。跟我来
- Have you tried ramming down the door? - You wait here. Follow me.
这么做也是没用的
It won't do any good.
- 科海根已经将通道减压 - 那就打通往M区的路
- Cohaagen depressurized the tunnels. - Then drill through to Section M.
我们办不到 空气已快耗尽了
We can't. we're running out of air.
我们需要援助
We need help.
好，再忍耐一下 梅琳娜刚刚带着魁德到达此地
Okay, sit tight. melina just got here with Quaid.
我希望他值得我们如此牺牲
I hope he was worth it.
我也是
So do I.
- 很高兴你们能及时赶来 - 你看来不怎么高兴
- I'm glad you made it. - You don't look glad.
科海根封了维纳斯城。还停止供应空气
Cohaagen sealed up Venusville. he shut off the air.
你一定是知道某些重要的秘密，魁德
You must know something pretty damn important, Quaid.
他要你
He wants you.
如果我们不把你交出去 到了明早这一区的人都将没命
If we don't hand you over, everybody in this sector will be dead by morning.
那么咱们也没什么选择的余地了
Then we don't have much choice, do we.
我们不能把他交出去
We can't turn him in.
这得让寡头来决定 跟我来吧！魁德
That's up to Kuato. come with me, Quaid.
坐
Sit down.
- 寡头在哪？ - 在赶来此地的途中
- Where's Kuato? - On his way.
你听过关于金字塔矿场的传闻吧？
You heard the rumors about the Pyramid Mine?
是的
Yeah.
科海根在那里面发现了某样东西 让他吓得要命
Cohaagen found something weird inside and it's got him scared shitless.
什么东西？外星人？
What? Aliens?
- 你说呢？ - 我不知道
- You tell me. - I don't know.
是的，你知道 所以我们才把你弄来这里
Yes, you do. that's why we brought you here.
科海根的大秘密...
Cohaagen's big secret is buried in that black hole...
埋在你的脑里
you call a brain.
寡头将要把它掘出来
And Kuato's gonna dig it out.
- 你就是寡头，对吧？ - 错了
- You're Kuato, right? - Wrong.
寡头是个变种人 当你见到他时可别大惊小怪
Kuato's a mutant, so don't get upset when you see him.
你想要什么？魁德先生
What do you want, Mr. Quaid?
和你要的一样，恢复记忆
Same as you: to remember.
但，又是为了什么？
But why?
- 为了能再成为我自己 - 你的所做所为决定你是什么人
- To be myself again. - You are what you do.
个人的价值端视他的所做所为
A man is defined by his actions...
而不是他的记忆
not his memory.
来请...
Please...
握住我的双手
take my hands.
现在，对我敞开你的心灵
Now open your mind to me.
拜托
Please.
敞开你的心灵…
Open your mind.
我们得在叛军启动它之前毁掉它
We should blow the thing up before the rebels turn it on.
我认为咱们可试着将它启动 看看会有何结果
I say we throw the switch and see what happens.
- 别傻了！ - 我们不能冒这种险
- Don't be an idiot. - We can't risk it.
引发的连锁反应 可能会毁掉这星球上所有的Ｔ矿
The chain reaction could spread to all the terbinium in the planet.
也就是熔毁 整个星球都可能会熔毁
That means a meltdown, a meltdown on a planetary scale.
你想造这玩意的人没想到这点?
Don't you think whoever built this thing thought of that?
谁晓得它们是怎么想的? 它们又不是人类
Who knows what the hell they thought? they weren't human.
或许这是个陷井 或许它们就是要让这星球熔毁
Maybe it's a trap. maybe they want a meltdown.
我们甚至不知道这是否还能用
We don't even know if this piece of junk will work.
它的历史有多久？一百万年？五十万年？
What is it? a million? Half a million?
- 约有五十万年 - 是五十万年前造的
- About half a million. - Half a million years old.
我们只需不让寡头…
Let's make sure Kuato--
醒醒！醒醒！ 快点！醒过来啊！
Wake up! Wake up! come on, wake up!
他们找到我们了！该死！ 我们走吧！
They found us! Shit! Let's go!
快醒醒，清醒过来，快！
Wake up! Snap out of it! Now! Come on!
他们杀进来了
They found us!
- 大伙儿撤退！ - 梅琳娜！
- Everybody out! - Melina!
快走！走啊！
Get moving! Get out!
走啊！
Get out!
大伙儿撤退！走啊！
Everybody out! Get out!
到气闸去！跟我来！
Get to the air lock! Follow me!
班尼！快来啊！
Benny, come on!
- 班尼！ - 我来了！
- Benny! - I'm coming!
穿上宇宙飞行服，我们到外面去！
Put these spacesuits on! we're going outside!
班尼，快点
Benny, hurry.
恭喜你，魁德…
Congratulations, Quaid.
你终于带领我们找到了他
You led us right to him.
你怎能这么做！你也是个变种人
How can you do this? you're a mutant.
我还有四个孩子要养
I got four kids to feed.
第五个到哪里去了？
So what happened to number five?
妈的，你终于抓到我的破绽了
Ah, shit, man. You got me.
我根本就还没结婚
I ain't even married.
现在把手举起来！
Now put your fucking hands in the air!
魁德…
Quaid.
别白费力气了，兄弟 他的算命生涯已经结束了
Forget it, man. his fortunetelling days are over.
启动…那个反应炉
Start the reactor.
解放火星…
Free Mars.
科海根先生想跟你谈谈
Mr. Cohaagen would like to talk to you.
原来这就是那位伟人
So this is the great man.
难怪他总能躲过我们的耳目
No wonder he kept out of sight.
我的好兄弟…
Well, my boy...
你是个英雄！
you're a hero.
操你的
Fuck you.
不必谦虚，如今寡头已经死了！
Don't be modest.
叛军已全部被消灭 而你则是最大的功臣
The resistance has been completely wiped out, and you were the key to the whole thing.
他在骗人
He's lying.
你这该死的两面人！
You two-faced bastard.
别怪他，安其儿 他的确是无辜的
You can't blame him, angel. he's innocent.
是这样的，魁德… 我的手下没有一个能接近寡头
You see, Quaid, none of my people could get close to Kuato.
那些该死的变种人 总是能闻出我们的气味
Fucking mutants could always sniff us out.
于是豪瑟和我经过一番思考后 将你创造出来，一个完美的卧底计划
So Hauser and I sat down and invented you, the perfect mole.
你根本就是张眼说瞎话 豪瑟已经背叛了你
You know you're lying. hauser turned against you.
我们就是要让你这么想的
That's what we wanted you to think.
事实是，豪瑟自愿来扮演道格?魁德
The fact is, Hauser volunteered to become Doug Quaid.
唯有这方法才能骗过那些通灵人
It was the only way to fool the psychics.
别说笑了
Get your story straight.
自从我去过瑞可公司后 你手下这些白痴一直在追杀我
This idiot here has been trying to kill me ever since l went to Rekall.
你怎么可能要杀你派去卧底的人
You don't kill somebody you're trying to plant.
这并非计划中的一部份 是你自己要去瑞可而坏了事
He wasn't in on it. you set him off by going to Rekall.
- 那么为何我还活着？ - 我们一路上提供你许多帮助
- So why am l still alive? - We gave you lots of help.
- 比方说班尼 - 这是我的荣幸，兄弟
- Benny here. - My pleasure, man.
那个拿手提箱给你的人，面具，钱
The guy with the suitcase, the mask, the money...
以及豪瑟所留的话… 这一切全是我们所安排的
the message from Hauser, all of that was set up by us.
抱歉，这说法太完美了
Sorry. Too perfect.
完美个屁！
Perfect, my ass!
你在我们还没来得及派你上场前 就开启了你的记忆
You pop your memory cap before we can activate you.
让瑞克特到处追杀你 破坏了我花了一年准备的计划
Richter goes hog-wild, screwing up everything I spent a year planning.
老实说 这计划能成功连我都感到意外
Frankly, I'm amazed it worked.
科海根…
Well, Cohaagen...
我真是服了你 这是我所听过最精彩的故事
I have to hand it to you. It's the best mind-fuck yet.
不先别这么快就下结论
Well, don't take my word for it.
- 某个你所信任的人要跟你说话 - 这一回又是谁？
-Someone you trust wants to talk to you. -Who is it this time?
我母亲？
My mother?
你好，魁德
Howdy, Quaid.
如果你听见这段话 就表示寡头已死
If you're listening to this, that means Kuato is dead...
而你也带领我们找到了他
and you have led us to him.
我就知道你一定不会让我失望
I knew you wouldn't let me down.
抱歉让你吃了这么多苦头
Sorry for the shit I've put you through, but hey...
但朋友本来就该互相帮忙的
what are friends for?
我很想祝你永远快乐，长命百岁，老朋友...
I would like to wish you happiness and long life, old buddy...
但不幸的是，这是不可能的
but unfortunately, this is not gonna happen.
要知道，你占用的身体是我的 我现在得要回来
You see, it's my body you've got there and I want it back.
抱歉，有借就有还 那身体本来就是我的
Sorry to be an Indian giver, but I was here first.
那么，永别了，朋友
So adios, amigo.
谢谢你没让自己送命
And thanks for not getting yourself killed.
或许咱们还会在梦里见面呢！
Hey, maybe we'll meet in our dreams.
谁晓得会怎样？
You'll never know.
你们这些混蛋！
You bastards!
放开我！
Let go of me!
- 准备好了？ - 全检查过了
- Ready? - Auto.
全准备好了，长官
- Check. - Ready to go, sir.
放轻松点，魁德
Relax, Quaid.
- 你会喜欢当豪瑟的 - 那家伙是个该死的混蛋！
- You'll like being Hauser. - The guy's a fucking asshole.
这不是真的 他是我最要好的朋友之一
Not true. He's one of my best friends.
更何况他有一栋大房子，一辆宾土汽车
Besides, he's got a big house and a Mercedes.
你喜欢梅琳娜，对吧？ 你今后每晚都可以干她
And you like Melina, right? You'll get to fuck her every night.
是的… 她将成为豪瑟的心肝宝贝
That's right. She's going to be Hauser's babe.
我会打烂他的卵蛋
I'll bust his balls.
不，公主…
Uh-uh, princess.
我们要将你改变一下
We're having you fixed.
你将学会尊敬，顺从…
You're gonna be respectful, compliant...
晓得该感激 这些都是女人该具有的美德
and appreciative. The way a woman should be.
科海根先生，你的电话
Mr. Cohaagen, telephone.
是的，什么事
Yes? What is it?
长官，G区的氧气已降到最低点
Sir. The oxygen level is bottoming out in Sector G.
你要我接下来怎么做？
What do you want me to do about it?
- 什么也别做 - 但他们支持不到一个钟头了，长官
- Don't do anything. - But they won't last an hour, sir.
管他们去死！
Fuck them.
可以让别区的人作为警戒
It'll be a good lesson to the others.
别这样，科海根！你已达到你的目的 给这些人空气吧
Come on, Cohaagen! You got what you want. give these people air.
我的朋友，再过五分钟 你就不会关心这些人的死活了
My friend, in five minutes you won't give a shit about the people.
开始吧！大夫
Fire it up, Doc.
对不起！大夫
Excuse me, Doctor.
- 他将会记得这一切吗？ - 完全不会
- Is he gonna remember any of this? - Not a thing.
真的？
Oh, really?
对了，魁德 我今晚要举行派对
Oh, Quaid, I'm having a party tonight.
你可以带梅琳娜一起来 提醒他一下，大夫
Why don't you and Melina drop by. Remind him, Doc.
- 我会的 - 派对上见了
- Sure. - See you at the party.
别挣扎。你越反抗只会越痛苦
Keep still. fighting just makes it hurt.
如果你不安静下来会精神错乱的
If you don't keep still, you'll end up psychotic.
不！
Hey, don't!
梅琳娜，支持住！
Melina, hold on!
你还好吧？ 你仍是原来的你吗？
Are you all right? Are you still you?
我也不怎么确定，亲爱的。你想呢？
I'm not sure, dear. What do you think?
咱们快离开这里吧！
Let's get the hell out of here.
你得做个决定才行，长官
You have to make a decision, sir.
杀了他
Kill him.
也该是时候了！
It's about goddamn time.
- 你要上哪去？ - 去找那反应炉
- Where are you going? - To the reactor.
- 什么反应炉？ - 在矿坑里的那个，快点！
- What reactor? - The one in the mines. Come on!
那些人都快死了啊！魁德 快停下来，我们得给他们空气
People are dying, Quaid! Stop! We've got to get air!
那反应炉能制造空气 这就是科海根的大秘密，我们走
The reactor makes air. that's Cohaagen's secret. Let's go.
这个反应炉又是从哪来的？
Where's this reactor come from?
- 外星人造的 - 外星人？
- Aliens built it. - Aliens?
- 你确定它有用吗？ - 它就在前面
- Are you sure about this? - It's just up ahead.
被封住了
What the hell--
魁德！魁德！
Quaid!
嗨，魁德，你还记得我吧？
Hey, Quaid, you remember me?
是班尼，班尼就是我的名字
Benny! Benny's the name! Hahahaha.
这个厉害！
Oh, that's good!
我要把你们开膛破肚！
I'm gonna drill you, sucker!
我要把你们绞成肉泥！
I'm gonna grind you up!
我来了！
I'm coming!
我来找你了！宝贝
I'm coming for you, baby!
这他妈的怎么回事？
What the fuck is this?
这个该死的火星废物！
Damn this piece of Martian junk!
魁德，我要把你压扁！
Hey, Quaid, I'm gonna squash you!
班尼，尝尝这个吧！
Benny, here!
你他妈的在哪里？
Where the fuck are you?
我钻死你！
Screw you!
魁德！快到这边来
Quaid, get over here!
什么事？
What is it?
这边打通了一个缺口
There's an opening.
我就知道
I knew it.
这整个东西 就是个以T矿制成的反应炉
This whole thing is one big reactor made out of terbinium.
科海根知道它可以制造氧气 但那混蛋却不肯将它启动！
Cohaagen knows it makes air. the bastard won't turn it on.
当然了
Of course not.
如果火星有了大气层，他就无法再统治了
If Mars had an atmosphere, he'd lose control.
看到那下面没？
See down there?
那是一条冰河
It's a glacier.
整个火星的核心都是冰
The whole core of Mars is ice.
反应炉把冰融化
The reactor melts it...
就会释放出氧气来
and it releases the oxygen.
来吧
Come on.
- 足够让所有的人呼吸？ - 当然
- Enough for everyone to breathe? - Sure.
足以供给整个星球使用
Enough for the whole planet.
如果咱们能及时将它启动的话
If we turn it on on time.
上！快！
Come on. Come on!
慢着
Hold on.
开枪！
Now!
狗娘养的！
Son of a bitch.
快退开！
Go!
他身上有全息国装置！
He's got a hologram!
你们以为这是真的魁德吗？ 是真的
You think this is the real Quaid? It is.
我要死也得带你一起死！
Now, you're coming with me!
派对上见了！瑞克特
See you at the party, Richter.
别碰那东西！
Don't touch that!
到一边去！退后！
Get away! Get back!
你怕什么？
What are you afraid of?
- 将它启动啊！ - 这是不可能的！
- Turn it on. - Impossible!
一旦连锁反应产生 这星球上的T矿全将被毁
Once the reaction starts, it'll spread to all the terbinium in the planet.
整个火星也将熔毁
Mars will go into global meltdown.
所以外星人才从未使用过它
That's why the aliens never turned it on.
你以为我会相信你吗？
And you expect me to believe you?
谁在乎你相不相信？ 再过30秒你就没命了
Who gives a shit what you believe? In 30 seconds you'll be dead.
然后我将炸了这个地方 回家去吃麦片
Then I'll blow this place up and be home in time for corn flakes.
我本来也不希望见到这种结局
I didn't want it to end this way.
我要豪瑟回来，但事与愿违…
I wanted Hauser back. But no.
你偏要当魁德！
You had to be Quaid!
- 我本来就是魁德 - 你什么也不是！
- I am Quaid. - You're nothing!
你什么人也不是！ 只是一场愚笨的梦
You're nobody! You're a stupid dream.
所有的梦都是会结束的
Well, all dreams come to an end.
梅琳娜，别松手
Melina, hold on!
不！别这么做！
Don't do it!
我们全都会死！
We'll all die!
所有的人通通会死！
Everybody will die!
魁德！
Quaid!
我真不敢相信，这就像一场梦
I can't believe it. It's like a dream.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
我刚刚想到一个可怕的念头。 如果这一切真的是一场梦呢？
I just had a terrible thought. What if this is a dream?
那就趁梦醒前赶快吻我吧！
Well, then kiss me quick before you wake up.
剧终